[rock guitar riff playing]
‎莉亚 赶紧拍吧
[Gwen, straining] Leia, take the picture.
‎我的眼睛好疼 我需要眨眼
My eyes are burning. I need to blink.
‎这台相机只能拍24张照片
‎我一张都不想浪费
There's only 24 pictures on this camera,
and I don't want to waste any of them.
[shutter clicks]
‎23张 我刚刚拍了一张奥兹的屁股
Twenty-three.
I just took one of Ozzie's butt.
‎给我一张 我总是找不到好角度
Send me a copy.
I can never get a good angle.
‎不如让我来拍吧？
Why don't I take the pictures?
‎哦太棒了 尽量把我拍酷一点
Oh great! Try to make me look really cool.
‎这只是台相机而已
It's just a camera.
‎准备好狂欢了吗？
Ready to party?
‎我带了小吃 内特带了桶酒
I got the snacks. Nate's got the keg.
[loud clanging]
‎抱歉
Sorry!
[panting]
‎我撞上了张蜘蛛网
‎结果她就从我手中滚下去了
I walked into a spiderweb,
and she got away from me.
‎老兄 这可是莉亚的最后一晚
‎你就把国庆节那个恶心酒桶拿来了？
Dude, it's Leia's last night,
‎老兄 这可是莉亚的最后一晚
‎你就把国庆节那个恶心酒桶拿来了？
and you brought that nasty keg
from Fourth of July?
‎我可是把这桶酒
‎当成自己的孩子一样照顾
I took care of this thing
like it's my baby.
‎直到我把它摔下了台阶
Till I dropped it down the stairs.
‎就像妈妈之前对你做的？
Just like Mom did to you?
‎呛爆！
Burn!
‎-老兄
Bro.
‎老兄
‎陈年、寡淡、臭烘烘的啤酒？
Old, flat, skunky beer?
‎我们也没那么饥不择食吧
We are not this desperate.
-["I Wish" plays]
-♪ I wish I was a little bit taller ♪
♪ I wish I was a baller ♪
♪ I wish I had a girl who looked good
I would call her ♪
♪ I wish I had a rabbit in a hat
With a bat ♪
-♪ And a six-four Impala ♪
-[shutter clicks]
♪ I wish I was like six-foot-nine
So I can get with Leoshi ♪
♪ 'Cause she don't know me
But yo, she's really fine ♪
♪ You know I see her all the time
Everywhere I go ♪
♪ And even in my dreams
I can scheme of ways to make her mine ♪
-♪ 'Cause I know she's livin' phat ♪
-[song ends]
‎我真觉得自己跳舞跳得很棒
I think I'm a really good dancer.
‎这是你的最后一晚 所以 确实
It's your last night, so… sure.
‎奥兹 我走了你会伤心吗？
Ozzie, are you gonna be sad when I'm gone?
Uh…
‎不会
No.
‎他不怎么善于表达自己的感受
He isn't great
about expressing his emotions.
‎如果我表达了自己的感受
‎人们就会表达他们的感受
If I say how I feel,
people say how they feel.
‎关我屁事
And I don't care.
‎好吧 这是给完美夏日
‎画上完美句点的最后一晚
Well, this is the perfect last night
to cap off the perfect summer.
‎我要为此干一杯
I'll drink to that.
‎老兄 我本来还很担心
‎你跟莉亚说了要分手
[chuckles] Bro.
‎老兄 我本来还很担心
‎你跟莉亚说了要分手
I was worried when you had that talk
with Leia about breaking things off,
‎会把气氛搅得一团糟
it was gonna harsh the mood.
‎居然没有
But it didn't!
‎我玩得很开心
I'm having a blast!
[chuckles]
‎我还没告诉她呢
I haven't told her yet.
‎什么？
What?
-[shutter clicks]
-[rock music plays]
‎一 二 三 四
One, two, three, four!
‎在街上闲逛
♪ Hangin' out down the street ♪
‎和上周没什么两样
♪ The same old thing we did last week ♪
‎没什么事好做 就跟你唠唠嗑
♪ Not a thing to do ♪
♪ But talk to you ♪
‎这样挺好 这样挺好
♪ We're all all right! ♪
‎（90 年代秀）
‎你好 威斯康辛！
[young woman] Hello, Wisconsin!
‎-你要跟我分手？
‎-不 别这么说
-You're breaking up with me?
-No, no, no. Don't say it like that.
‎这并不是分手
It's not a breakup.
‎更像是我们之前是男女朋友
It's like we were boyfriend
and girlfriend,
‎现在我们得叫停了
but we're gonna stop.
‎这就是分手 你个蠢货
That's a breakup, you donk!
‎我的天哪 我只是
‎你的暑期艳遇之一 你这混蛋
Oh my God, I'm one of
your summer things, you jerk.
‎哇 她给你的鸡鸡裹了层酪酪
Whoa. She cheesied your deezy.
‎莉亚 不是我混蛋
Leia, I'm not being a jerk.
‎可我们要分开九个月
We're gonna be apart for nine months.
‎异地恋真的很难坚挺下去
Long distance relationships are hard.
‎坚挺
[chuckles] Hard.
‎我不想让我们承受这种痛苦
I don't want to put us through that.
‎所以就这样了吗？
‎我们连试都不试一下？
So that's it? We're not even gonna try?
‎莉亚 我知道你很生气
‎但他说的很有道理
Leia, I know you're upset,
but he's making a lot of sense.
‎这样你们就都能
‎毫无负担各管各的了 对吗 宝贝？
This way you both can go off
and live your lives. Right, babe?
‎是啊 异地恋可操蛋了
Yeah, long distance is nuts.
‎操蛋
Nuts. [chuckles]
[Jay gulps]
‎胆小鬼确实不适合异地恋
It's not for the faint of heart.
‎你知道我给在加拿大的男朋友
‎打电话要花多少钱吗？
Do you know how much it costs
to call my boyfriend in Canada?
‎呵 你爷爷奶奶很快就会发现的
Well, your grandparents
are about to find out.
‎格温 来帮我说句话
Gwen, help me out here.
‎他说的有道理
He has a point.
‎你居然赞同他们？
You're with them?
‎不 我只是为你着想
No, I'm looking out for you.
‎我是说 你们要分开很长一段时间
‎而且他又是个…浪货
I mean, it is a long time apart, and also…
‎我是说 你们要分开很长一段时间
‎而且他又是个…浪货
man-whore.
‎-难以置信！
‎-莉亚…
-Unbelievable!
-Leia…
‎别跟着我 我可不怕用上这玩意儿
Do not follow me!
I am not afraid to use this thing!
[rock music playing]
‎别挂 我去叫她
Hold on. Let me get her.
‎莉亚 有电话！
Leia, phone!
‎我还以为既然莉亚要走了
‎你肯定心情不好
I thought you'd be in a worse mood,
what with Leia leaving.
‎我是很难过 但后来
‎我意识到她不会离开太久
I was upset, but then I realized
she won't be gone for long.
‎她的男朋友在这里
Her boyfriend is here,
‎她最好的朋友住隔壁
‎她也喜欢我的土豆沙拉
her best friend lives next door,
‎她最好的朋友住隔壁
‎她也喜欢我的土豆沙拉
and she loves my potato salad.
‎那我呢？我也很风趣呀
And what about me? I'm fun.
‎嘿 奶奶
Hey, Grandma.
‎嗨 甜心 是杰伊打来的
Hi, sweetie. It's Jay.
Oh.
‎你这个烂人
-You suck!
-[phone dings]
‎哦 天啊
Oh dear.
‎嘿 莉亚 你感觉好点了吗？
Hey, Leia. You feeling any better?
[phone ringing]
[loud clanging]
‎我…我没觉得她好点了
Oh, I just… I… I don't think she is.
‎好吧 所以这是怎么回事？
Okay, so what's going on here?
‎男朋友的问题 我的问题
Boyfriend stuff, me stuff,
‎昨天她还因为
‎吃了几口奇怪的土豆沙拉犯恶心了
and yesterday she got sick
from some weird potato salad.
‎我的天啊 这都是十分严重的大问题
Oh my God! Those are the big-ticket items!
‎明年夏天她可能
‎都不想回来了 我得跟她谈谈
She may not want to come back
next summer. I gotta talk to her.
‎祝你好运
Good luck.
‎哦 别啊
Oh no.
‎大家都别走啊
Don't everyone leave.
‎那就只剩我和我的报纸了
Then it'll just be me and my newspaper.
[tree trunk cracking]
[loud thud]
‎你的树可能会害死人的 我应该告你
Your tree could've killed someone.
I should sue.
‎我的树？
My tree?
‎这棵树可是从你家来的
That tree came from your property.
‎这就是我们说的“凡事皆有定数”
‎再好的人也可能会遇上这种事
Oh, then we'll call it an act of God.
Could've happened to the best of us.
‎但这可不是什么好人的树
But it didn't happen to the best of us.
‎这可是你的树
It happened to you.
‎我一直在跟你说这棵树已经烂掉了
I have been telling you
that this tree is rotting,
‎你得好好把它处理掉
and you need to take care of it.
‎我一直很忙
I've been busy.
‎忙着干什么？
Doing what?
‎忙着干我
That would be me.
‎拜托！
Oh, come on!
‎你明明有时间把裤子穿上的
You had time to put on pants.
‎我的裤子得费点功夫才能穿进去
My pants take time to wiggle into.
‎有时我还得在大腿上抹点油
Sometimes I have to, uh, grease my thighs.
‎你就看上了这货？
This is attractive to you?
‎我们在奇利斯餐厅
‎偶遇了对方 决定再交往一次试试
We bumped into each other at the Chili's,
and we decided to give it another try.
‎事实证明我想要…
‎我的宝贝回来 宝贝回来
Yeah, it turned out I wanted…
♪ My baby back, baby back ♪
‎我们能回到树的问题上来吗？
Could we get back to the tree?
‎你得联系你的房东 把这个处理掉
You need to get ahold of your landlord
and get rid of this.
‎那家伙可是朵奇葩
Oh, that guy's a real piece of work.
‎你能跟他谈谈吗？
‎你很擅长冲人大吼大叫
Can you talk to him?
You're so good at yellin' at people.
‎好吧 我来处理
Fine, I'll take care of it.
‎谢谢 你真是我的救星
‎我现在就打电话给他
Thanks, Red. You're a lifesaver.
I'll go call him right now.
‎我马上就过去
[Fez murmurs] I'll be right in.
‎-你就这么喜欢灭我威风吗？
‎-什么？
-Did you do have fun cutting off my balls?
-What?
‎应该由我来对付房东
I should be the one
dealing with the landlord.
‎我要让雪莉看到
‎我对我们的关系很用心
I need Sherri to see
that I am invested in our relationship.
‎好吧 赶紧去给房东打电话
Fine, call the landlord.
‎只要把这棵树从我车道上挪走就行
Just get this tree outta my driveway.
‎哦 雷德先生
Oh, Mr. Red!
[Fez gasps]
‎搞什么鬼？
-What the hell?!
-[Fez yelps]
‎我不知道你听说了什么
‎但是…要看得花钱
I don't know what you heard,
but… this show ain't free.
‎他们吃了我的冰棒
‎占领了我的地下室
They eat my popsicles,
they take over my basement,
‎还把我的生活搅得天翻地覆
and they turn my life upside down.
‎全是蠢蛋
Dumbasses!
‎好吧 现在你说话越来越像你爷爷了
Okay, now you're starting
to sound like your grandpa.
‎别忘了你有多喜欢这里
‎还有你已经等不及要回来了
Let's not forget how much you love it here
and how you can't wait to come back.
‎回来？我只想离开这个…
‎破破烂烂、名不见经传的小镇
Come back?
‎回来？我只想离开这个…
‎破破烂烂、名不见经传的小镇
I… I just want to get out of this…
this crappy Podunk town.
‎好吧 我倒是
‎在点域镇开创了相当美好的生活
Well, I have carved out
a pretty nice life here in Point Place.
‎但我想这不重要
But I guess that doesn't matter.
‎喂 我知道我来早了
Hey. I know I'm early.
‎妈妈
Mom. [gasps]
‎我在路上想打电话来
I tried to call,
‎但听上去像是有人把听筒扔进了锅里
but it sounded like someone was
banging the phone around in a pot.
‎妈妈 谢天谢地你来了
Mom, thank God you're here.
‎一切都糟糕透顶
Everything's ruined.
‎我男朋友跟我分手了
‎然后 出于某种原因
‎我把气撒在了格温身上
My boyfriend broke up with me,
and for some reason I took it out on Gwen.
‎-男朋友？
‎-杰伊凯尔索
-Boyfriend?
-Jay Kelso.
‎凯尔索？
Kelso?
‎我们一直在通话
‎这些事你都不跟我提一句吗？
We talk all the time.
You don't mention any of this?
‎嗯 没有 我认为…真正重要的是
Well, no, I think…
I think what is truly important here
‎这个夏天莉亚过得十分开心
is that Leia had a hoot this summer.
‎可她似乎都忘记了
Which she seems to be forgetting.
‎电影之夜 湖畔小屋之旅 锐舞派对…
Movie nights,
trips to the lake house, the rave--
‎-锐舞派对？
‎-别这么古板 唐娜
-A rave?
-Oh, don't be such a square, Donna.
‎听着 我会在车上好好跟你解释的
Look, I'll explain everything in the car.
‎现在我得离开这个鬼地方
Right now I just need
to get out of this hellhole.
‎好吧 鬼地方会有
‎这么朗朗上口的广告吗？
Well, would a hellhole have
such a catchy commercial?
‎一切都点向了这个区域
♪ Everything points to this place ♪
‎-让我…跟她聊聊？
‎-好吧
-Let me… talk to her for a sec?
Fine.
[Kitty hesitates]
‎乔治哈里森的姐姐也住在这里
George Harrison's sister lived here.
‎妈妈 我…觉得自己好蠢
Mom, I… [scoffs]
I feel so stupid.
‎我以为我度过了一个完美的夏天…
I thought I was having
this perfect summer, and…
‎现在全都糟糕透顶
now it's all ruined.
‎亲爱的 分手是很糟糕
Honey, breakups suck.
‎你怎么知道？
‎你从高中就和爸爸在一起了
How would you know?
You've been with Dad since high school.
‎-事实上 我们分手了很多次
‎-是吗？
-Actually, we broke up a lot.
-You did?
‎没错 有一次我还
‎跟杰伊的叔叔凯西约会了
Yeah, and one of those times
I dated Jay's uncle, Casey.
‎凯尔索家的人？
A Kelso?
‎对
Yeah.
‎听着 青少年的生活确实是一团糟
Look, being a teenager gets messy.
‎但每当我饱受煎熬时
‎你知道是谁帮我度过了难关吗？
Whenever I was going through something,
you know who helped me through it?
‎是我的朋友们
My friends.
‎去和格温谈谈吧
So just go talk to Gwen.
‎凯尔索家到底有什么魔力？
What is it with these Kelsos?
‎-是发型
‎-我就知道 太完美了
-It's the hair.
-I know. It's so perfect.
-[both chuckling]
-[rock music playing]
‎再次感谢你帮我对付房东
Thanks again for helping me
deal with my landlord.
‎这是你做过最性感的事情了
That was the sexiest thing
you've ever done.
‎我是说 除了你说“开心果”的样子
I mean, besides the way
you say "pistachio."
Mmm…
‎开心果
-Pistachio.
-[Sherri moans]
‎我不知道发生了什么
‎但看起来太诡异了
I don't know what's happening,
but it seems weird.
‎格温 你还记得我的朋友菲丝吗？
Oh, Gwen. You remember my friend, Fez?
‎记得 你的“朋友”用光了我的沐浴露
Yeah, your "friend" used all my bodywash.
‎很高兴能认识另一位黄蜜瓜香味同好
It's so nice to meet
another fan of the cucumber-melon.
‎能给我20块钱吗？
‎我要给莉亚买个礼物
Can I have 20 bucks?
I need to get something for Leia.
‎哦 请让我来
Oh, allow me.
‎哦没错 我已经摸到了
Oh yeah, I feel it.
[strains, chuckles]
‎这是五十块
Fifty it is.
‎谢啦 新爸爸
Thanks, new Dad. [chuckles]
‎你真的是太贴心了
Oh, that was awful sweet of you.
‎嗯 我是麻烦终结者嘛 宝贝
Well, I'm a problem solver, baby.
[chuckles]
‎很好 因为房东来了
Oh. Good.
'Cause my landlord's here.
‎那么…
So…
Oh…
‎是你啊
It's you.
‎-芬顿 你来这儿干嘛？
‎-这地方是我的
-Fenton, what are you doing here?
-I own this place.
‎还有另外三套房子 一套复式公寓
‎和一家迪品多滋冰淇淋
Along with three other homes,
one duplex, and a Dippin' Dots.
‎没错 睁大眼睛好好看看 菲丝
Yeah. Take it all in, Fez.
‎这就是成功人士的模样
This is what success looks like.
‎我知道成功人士长啥样
‎你听说过菲丝轩吗？
Oh, I know what success looks like.
Have you heard of Chez Fez?
‎勉强算听过吧 我在洗澡时
‎耐着性子看了你那烦人的广告
[scoffs] Barely.
‎勉强算听过吧 我在洗澡时
‎耐着性子看了你那烦人的广告
I sat through one of your annoying
commercials when I was in the bath.
‎我已经泡在浴盐里了
‎所以我不想爬起来换台
I'd already put in my salt, so I didn't
wanna get out and change the channel.
‎扯远了 不过这是
‎为了告诉你我浴室里有台电视 贱人
Which is a long way of saying
‎扯远了 不过这是
‎为了告诉你我浴室里有台电视 贱人
I have a TV in my bathroom, bitch.
‎好吧 该知道的
‎我们现在都已经知道了 我想…
Okay, then! Now that we're
all caught up on everything, I guess--
‎在你签署租约时
When you signed your lease,
‎已经明确说过
‎不得饲养体重超过68公斤的宠物
it specifically said
no pets over 150 pounds.
‎我只有67.5公斤
I'm 149!
‎包括这两条大腿？
With those thighs?
‎-我这两条大腿总好过你那张脸
‎-我这张脸总好过你那双鞋
-I'd rather these thighs than that face.
-I'd rather this face than those shoes.
‎-我这双鞋总好过没头发
‎-下地狱去吧！
-I'd rather these shoes than no hair.
-[gasps] Go to hell!
‎那就地狱见！
I'll see you there!
‎我们别把事情搞那么复杂
‎我们还得处理那棵树
Let's not get our panties in a bunch.
We still gotta deal with that tree.
‎在你付清房租之前
‎我是不会碰那棵树的
[chuckles] I'm not touching that tree
until you pay your rent.
‎-并且就因为这货 我还要涨房租
‎-什么？
-Which just went up because of that.
-What?
‎另外 离我的迪品多滋冰淇淋远一点
And stay the hell away from
my Dippin' Dots!
‎你永远也别想尝到未来的冰淇淋了
You will never taste
the ice cream of the future.
‎-开心…
‎-我没这个心情
-Pistach--
-I am not in the mood!
[rock music playing]
‎嗨 杰伊
Hi, Jay.
‎福尔曼太太？
Mrs. Forman?
‎我们该聊聊了
It's time we had a little chat.
‎你怎么知道我在这里？
How did you know I was here?
‎这可是我的小镇 亲爱的
‎到处都有我的眼线
Oh, this is my town, sweetie.
I have eyes everywhere.
‎莉亚怎么样了？
How's Leia doing?
‎我是说 弄成现在这样
‎我很过意不去 可又没办法
I mean, I feel really bad about
how things went down, but I had to do it.
‎这就是我想跟你聊的
Well, that is what
I wanted to talk to you about.
‎她很生气
‎明年夏天她可能不会回来了
She is so upset,
she may not come back next summer.
‎-这不是我想要的结果
‎-这跟你无关
That's not what I wanted.
‎-这不是我想要的结果
‎-这跟你无关
This isn't about you!
[forced laughter]
‎不 其实这跟你有关 亲爱的
‎你刚才在说什么来着？
No, no, it is about you, honey.
You were saying?
‎我没想伤害她 福尔曼太太
I wasn't trying to hurt her, Mrs. Forman.
‎只是 你知道的 任何事都有可能发生
‎要是她遇到了别人该怎么办？
It's just, you know, anything can happen.
What if she meets someone else?
‎要是我被邀请出演
‎下一部《小子难缠》该怎么办？
Or what if I get asked
to star in the next Karate Kid?
‎我是说 我得搬到里西达去了！
I mean, I'd have to move to Reseda!
‎好吧
Okay, okay.
‎让我来跟你讲讲
‎我的一个异地恋小故事
Let me tell you a little story about
a long distance relationship of mine.
‎当时我正在和一个男孩子约会
‎我疯狂地爱着他
I was dating this boy
I was madly in love with.
‎然后战争开始了 他被派往了国外
And then the war started.
He was being shipped overseas.
‎第一次世界大战？
World War I?
[sharp exhale]
‎总之 我们决定还是得试试看
Anyway, we decided
we would still give it a shot.
‎我从来没有为这个决定感到后悔
And I never regretted that decision.
‎这家伙是雷德吗？
And that guy was Red?
‎不 我记得他叫史蒂夫
No, I think his name was Steve.
‎所以你的重点是异地恋是行不通的？
So your point is
long distance doesn't work?
‎跟史蒂夫行不通
Not with Steve.
‎他的肚脐眼超大
He had a giant belly button.
‎我透过他的毛衣都能看得到
I could see it through his sweaters.
‎重点是 至少我们试过了
The point is, at least we tried.
‎亲爱的 千万别一辈子
‎都在纠结本该发生什么
Honey, don't go through life
wondering what could have been.
‎你把我的手捏得太紧了 福尔曼太太
You're squeezing my hand pretty hard,
Mrs. Forman. [chuckles]
‎我真的希望你能试试
I really want you to give it a try.
‎越来越紧了
It's getting tighter.
‎我可是拧开过不少蛋黄酱罐子
I open a lot of mayonnaise jars.
[rock guitar riff playing]
Shh.
‎一只苍蝇落在了我的裤裆
‎我正在考虑是否值得给它来一下
A fly landed on my crotch, and I'm trying
to decide if it's worth the swat.
‎可恶 它飞走了
-[fly buzzing]
-Damn. It flew away.
‎这可能算件好事
That's probably a good thing.
‎-格温在哪里？
‎-她出去了
-Oh, where's Gwen?
-She's out somewhere.
‎我不想不跟她道别就离开
I don't want to leave
without saying goodbye to her.
‎我反应太过头了
I totally overreacted.
‎这是我第一次分手 我处理得不太好
This is my first breakup,
and I'm not handling it too well.
‎没错 是很糟糕
Yeah, it sucks.
‎我第一次分手时感觉我的心脏
‎都要从屁股里掏出来了 所以…
My first breakup felt like my heart
was getting ripped out of my butt, so…
‎更糟糕的是 大家都赞同杰伊的做法
And it made it even worse
that everyone was agreeing with Jay.
‎并不是所有人
Not everyone.
‎听着 我当时很为难 因为杰伊
‎是我最好的朋友 但我赞同你的想法
Look, I was in a tough spot
'cause Jay's my best friend, but
‎听着 我当时很为难 因为杰伊
‎是我最好的朋友 但我赞同你的想法
I agree with you.
‎-是吗？
‎-对
-You do?
-Yeah.
‎然后妮基插话说这样就能各过各的了
And then Nikki chimed in
talking about living separate lives,
‎然后…我担心
‎我的心脏又得从屁股里掏出来
and… I got worried I'd get
my heart ripped out of my butt again.
‎拜托 她这人就是这样
Come on, Nate. That's just how she is.
‎我知道 我只是…
‎我希望她别总是那么…
I know. I just…
I wish she wasn't always so…
‎-天啊 我不知道该用什么词形容
‎-实际？
-God, there just isn't a word for it.
-Practical?
‎酷 我们刚刚发明了一个新词
Cool. We just invented a word!
‎嗯 谢谢你告诉我这些 内特
Well, thanks for telling me
all this, Nate.
‎很高兴知道这里
‎还有另一个无可救药的浪漫主义者
It's nice to know there's
another hopeless romantic out there.
‎对 我是说
‎还有什么能比爱更强大呢？
[chuckles] Yeah.
I mean, what's more powerful than love?
‎也许是闪电吧 但也就这样了
Maybe lightning. But that's it.
‎对 如果两个人命中注定要在一起
‎那他们什么难关都能熬过去
Right. If two people are meant to be,
then they can survive anything.
‎没错
Exactly.
‎你知道能找到
‎那个特别的人是有多幸运吗？
Do you know how lucky it is
to find that special person?
‎那个在一起能让你感到自在的人？
Someone who you feel comfortable with?
‎-那个可以跟你聊聊的人
‎-然后一切都是那么的轻松
-And someone you can talk to.
-And everything's just easy.
‎-对 我是说 那个能…
‎-理解你的人？
-Right. I mean, someone who just…
-Gets you?
‎-对
-Yeah.
‎搞什么鬼？
What the hell?!
‎-莉亚？
‎-格温？
-Leia?!
-Gwen?!
‎-内特？
‎-格温？
-Nate?!
-Gwen?!
‎有只苍蝇落在了我的蛋蛋上
There was a fly on my junk.
[rock music playing]
[chill rock music playing]
‎那个芬顿真是让我火冒三丈
Oh, that Fenton makes my blood boil.
‎但我也想陪在雪莉身边
But I also want to be there for Sherri.
‎太夸张了吗 亲爱的妈妈？
Oh, so much drama. Right, mama?
‎你是谁来着？
Who are you?
‎我觉得他在跟格温的妈妈上床
I think he's banging Gwen's mom.
‎没错
Yes.
‎没错 确实
Yes, I am.
‎我们刚刚才重燃爱火
Oh, and we had just rekindled
the flame to our relationship.
‎然后芬顿就把它踩灭了
Then Fenton just stomped it out.
‎哦 跟我一起痛哭吧
Oh, cry with me.
[sobbing]
‎抱歉 石头里是挤不出水来的
Sorry. I can't get water from a stone.
‎你们俩真是没用
Oh, you two are no help.
‎我想念我的小伙伴们
I miss my people.
[electric guitar riff plays]
‎也许这种生活
‎根本就不存在 你们发现了吗？
Maybe this life doesn't even matter,
you know?
‎也许我们根本不在这里
Maybe we're not even here.
‎或者 不对
‎也许我在这里 但你们都不在
Or, no. Maybe I'm here, but you're not.
‎喂？
[terrified gasp] Hello?
[laughing]
Oh!
‎天啊
Man.
‎我完全忘记了我为什么在笑
I just totally forgot why I was laughing.
‎这不是很好笑吗？
Isn't that funny? [coughs]
‎我已经对你失去耐心了 老兄
I'm losing my patience with you, man.
‎你得好好抓牢她
You gotta get with her.
‎我是说 没有什么能比
I mean, there's nothing more beautiful
‎两个人完美地结合在一起
‎更加美好的了 就像…
than when two people
fit together perfectly like…
‎嗯 就像这两片薯片…
Well, like two of these potato…
‎它们是怎么做到的？
How do they do this?!
‎就这样吗？
That's it?
‎我必须放下我对芬顿的怨恨
‎来修复我和雪莉的感情
I have to let go of my grudge with Fenton
to fix my relationship with Sherri.
‎菲丝 你在这里做什么？
Fez, what are you doing here?
‎唐娜？ 这真是太棒了 老朋友都来了
Donna? Oh, this is so great.
The old gang is here.
‎也许你该跟我们来呼吸点新鲜空气了
Maybe we should get you some fresh air.
‎唐娜 我做不到
Donna, Donna. I can't.
‎艾瑞克是我最好的朋友
Eric is my best friend.
[rock music playing]
‎-咋回事？
‎-我不知道
-How?
-I don't know.
‎-为啥啊？
‎-我不知道
-Why?
-I do not know.
‎他是杰伊最好的朋友
‎他是妮基的男朋友
[groans] He's Jay's best friend.
He's Nikki's boyfriend.
‎他是你哥哥
He's your brother.
Ugh!
‎真是太糟糕了
This is so bad.
[chuckles]
‎你在笑什么？
‎抱歉 我只是想到了
‎我们第一次来到这里的时候
-Why are you laughing?
-Sorry.
‎抱歉 我只是想到了
‎我们第一次来到这里的时候
I was just thinking about
the first time we came up here.
‎你从没喝过啤酒 也从没吻过别人
You'd never had a beer.
You'd never kissed anyone.
‎你一直在聊学校的辩论社
You never stopped
talking about debate club.
Oh…
‎我当时真是个傻瓜
I was such a dork.
‎但看看现在的你
‎简直就是麻烦的化身 我喜欢
But now look at you.
You're an agent of chaos. I love it.
‎格温 我现在该怎么办？
Gwen, what do I do now?
‎没啥可做的
There's nothing to do.
‎你没有吻内特 你也不欠杰伊什么
You didn't kiss Nate.
You don't owe Jay anything.
‎所以 现在 你就回芝加哥去
So, for now, you go back to Chicago,
‎然后每天都得给我打电话
you call me every freaking day,
‎我们尽可能地多见面
we see each other as much as we can,
‎然后明年夏天
‎你再回来 我们再来一遍
and then come back next summer,
and we do it all again.
‎我喜欢这个计划
I like this plan.
‎等等 我给你买了礼物
Hang on. I got you something.
‎想在离开前再犯一次法吗？
Wanna break one more law before you go?
‎来都来了 怎么会不想呢？
At this point, why the hell not?
[both laughing]
‎我不知道你对芬顿说了什么
‎但他居然彻底放手了
I don't know what you said to Fenton,
but he's completely backed off.
‎他会处理掉那棵树
‎还答应可以重铺浴室的地毯
He's getting rid of that tree,
and he promised to re-carpet the bathroom.
[Fez chuckles]
‎嗯 我喜欢你
‎所以我放下了自尊 向他赔礼谢罪了
Well, I like you,
‎嗯 我喜欢你
‎所以我放下了自尊 向他赔礼谢罪了
so I put my ego aside
and, uh, made him a peace offering.
‎好了 我已经搞定了那棵破烂桦树
Well, I made that birch my bitch.
‎看来我现在可以把这个脱下来了
Guess I can take this off now.
‎拍张照吧 你可以慢慢看
Take a picture. It'll last longer.
[Fez imitates shutter clicking]
-[laughs]
-[door shuts]
[Fez sighs contentedly]
‎这顶假发
‎是我从狗狗美容师那儿弄来的
I got that hair
from a dog groomer. [chuckles]
‎我赢了
I win.
‎嘿 谢谢你都帮我搞定了 菲丝
Hey, thanks for helping me out
with this, Fez.
‎大多数男人只会弃我而去
Most guys would have just
left me in the lurch.
‎听你这么说让我很激动
Oh, hearing you say that
makes me emotional.
‎这些激动都涌进了我的裤裆
And those emotions
are going into my pants.
‎我的身体真是个谜团
Oh, my body's such a puzzle.
‎好吧 那我们
‎就去卧室里好好探索一番吧
Well, let's go into the bedroom
and put our pieces together.
‎我本来想来一发的 但是…
Oh, I was hoping to have sex, but…
‎当然 无所谓 你想做啥就做啥
Sure, whatever.
Let's do what you wanna do.
[rock music playing]
‎-谢谢你为我做的一切 爷爷
‎-过来 孩子
-Thanks for everything, Grandpa.
-Come here, kiddo.
‎很高兴有你在身边
Loved having you around.
‎只有你
You.
‎告诉你的朋友们
‎你不在的时候 禁止进入地下室
But you tell your friends,
‎告诉你的朋友们
‎你不在的时候 禁止进入地下室
the basement is off-limits
while you're gone.
‎该我了！
My turn! My turn!
Oh!
‎我爱你 亲爱的
I love you, honey.
‎告诉你的朋友们 你不在的时候
[cooing] Tell your friends
they can use the basement
‎他们可以尽情来地下室玩
as much as they want while you're gone.
‎谢啦 奶奶 我也爱你
Thanks, Grandma. I love you too.
‎好了
-[laughs happily]
-[Leia] Okay!
‎爷爷 她抱得越来越紧了！
Grandpa, it's getting tighter!
‎凯蒂
Kitty!
‎她已经认输了
She's tappin' out.
‎嘿
Hey.
‎我们没必要聊这事 这没啥
We don't have to talk about it.
It was nothing.
‎没错
Right.
‎真的吗？
Really?
‎-不 还是有点啥的
‎-没错 绝对有点啥
-No, it was something.
-Yeah, it was definitely something.
‎莉亚！
Leia!
‎真高兴在你离开之前赶上了
I'm so glad I caught you before you left.
‎-嘿 兄弟
‎-没啥
-Oh. Hey, bro.
-Nothing.
‎你在这儿干嘛？
What are you doing here?
‎我进行了一下
‎自我反省 练了好久空手道
I did some soul-searching
and a crap ton of karate,
‎然后意识到我错了
and I realized I was wrong.
‎我还没准备好放弃我们
I'm not ready to give up on us.
‎我知道我是个混蛋
‎但如果你能再给我一次机会 莉亚
And… I know I was a jerk,
‎我知道我是个混蛋
‎但如果你能再给我一次机会 莉亚
but if you give me another chance, Leia,
‎之后的每一天我都会用来补偿你
I will spend every day
making it up to you.
‎杰伊这真是…太贴心了 我…
Jay, that's…
That's so sweet, I…
‎但我现在有点困惑
I'm just a little confused right now.
‎或许这样会有所帮助
Maybe this will help.
‎我真棒
That was a good one.
‎格温
Um, Gwen?
‎她到芝加哥之后会打电话给你的
She'll call you when she gets to Chicago.
‎-除非我先打给你
‎-行了 别得寸进尺了
-Not if I call you first.
-Okay, keep it moving.
‎好了 莉莉
‎最后的告别啦 我们得走了
Okay, Le-Le. Last goodbyes, we gotta go.
‎-你一到家就要给我打电话
‎-我们有很多要聊的
-You're calling me soon as you get home.
-Oh, we have a lot to talk about.
‎笑一个
Smile!
[shutter clicks]
‎这是最后一张照片啦
‎我的任务完成了
That was the last picture. My job is done.
‎我很抱歉
I am so sorry.
‎-什么？
‎-没什么
-What?
-Nothing.
‎快上车
Get in the car. Get in the car.
‎我绝对会很想她的
I'm really gonna miss her.
-[car engine starts]
-[Nate sighs]
‎我也会
Me too.
‎不会的
[snickers] Not.
‎莉亚 别走！
Leia, nooo!
‎没事的 伙计
It's okay, buddy.
-[sobbing]
-["Kids in America" by The Muffs playing]
‎回来吧 莉亚！回来吧！
Come back, Leia! Come baaack!
♪ Looking out a dirty old window ♪
♪ Outside the cars in the city
Go rushing by ♪
♪ I sit here alone and I wonder why ♪
♪ Friday night and everyone's moving ♪
♪ I can feel the heat
But it's soothing, heading down ♪
♪ I search for the beat
In this dirty town ♪
♪ Downtown the young ones are going ♪
‎（莉亚和格温 1995年）
♪ Downtown the young ones are growing ♪
-♪ We're the kids in America ♪
-♪ Whoa-oh ♪
♪ Everybody live for the music-go-round ♪
♪ Bright lights, the music gets faster ♪
♪ Look, boy, don't check on your watch
Not another glance ♪
♪ I'm not leaving now, honey
Not a chance ♪
♪ Hotshot, give me no problems ♪
♪ Much later, baby
You'll be saying never mind ♪
♪ You know life is cruel
Life is never kind ♪
♪ Kind hearts don't make a new story ♪
♪ Kind hearts don't grab any glory ♪
‎字幕翻译：Zeo Niu
-♪ We're the kids in America ♪
-♪ Whoa-oh ♪
‎字幕翻译：Zeo Niu
-♪ We're the kids in America ♪
-♪ Whoa-oh ♪
♪ Everybody live for the music-go-round ♪